thelordofporn.com 2019-08-02

# Privacy Policy - The Lord Of Porn

PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Websites or the Subscription Service.  
This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by www.thelordofporn.com

RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We do not retain any personal information until or unless the personal information is given to us by the user’s own consent through email or is submitted / stated or commented on our blog/forum. If we are given such information after such cases, we will either delete or anonymize your information or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.  
We shall retain Personal Information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, as long as is required in order to contact you about the Subscription Service or our other services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements).  
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information and / or any comment you made on our website we securely delete the information or anonymise it or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request.  
We may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. If you provide information as aforementioned to our affiliates (third party websites) we shall take no responsibility of the security of your personal data.

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM THE PEOPLE THAT VISIT OUR BLOG, WEBSITE OR APP  
If you contact us through a form or email, we will keep your name and email address confidential and we won’t share it with other parties. The only exception is if you contacted us to help you with an issue you had on one of the reviewed sites, and we need your personal data to help with resolving the issue.  
While we will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of the information you provide us, please write to us by email at info@thelordofporn.com or by mail to The Lord of Porn .

APPLICABILITY AND THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES SERVICES  
This Privacy Policy only applies to the information we collect when you use the Service or view the comments and does not apply to any website that uses the Service or other website linked to or from the Service. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, including Partner Sites, or the information or content contained thereon. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer applicable, it also does not apply to the Partner Site on which you are commenting. Your browsing activity and interaction with any other website, including those that link to or from the Service, is subject to that website’s privacy policy.

PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION  
This Website is a free service for surfers that does not require registration or the submission of any personal information to use the Website. We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit or subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Website from time to time. Accessing third party websites through our website shall give you a discount by the third party websites where they may ask you your personal information. If you provide information as aforementioned to our affiliates (third party websites) we shall take no responsibility of the security of your personal data.  
Users may, however, visit our Website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website related activities.

USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to:  
• Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Websites and to improve the Subscription Service;

• Send information of www.thelordofporn.com content to you which we think may be of interesting to you by post, email, or other means and send you marketing communications relating to our business;  
• Promote use of our services to you and share promotional and information content with you in accordance with your communication preferences;  
• Provide other companies with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;  
• Send information to you regarding changes to our Customer Terms of Service, Privacy Policy (including the Cookie Policy), or other legal agreements;  
• We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your Personal Information to the third party.  
We use the information collected through our Subscription Service by our customers for:  
• To provide the Subscription Service (which may include the detection, prevention and resolution of security and technical issues);  
• To respond to customer support requests; and  
• Otherwise to fulfill the obligations under the www.thelordofporn.com Customer Terms of Service

NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users, means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information.

LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION (EEA VISITORS ONLY)  
If you are a visitor/customer located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), we shall be the data controller of your personal information. Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at info@thelordofporn.com.  
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will not normally collect personal information from you and will only collect the personal data where you yourself give us consent through email and/or in the comment section mentioning your personal data and or otherwise detailed in this privacy policy. We may collect data where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.  
If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make it clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.  
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA, Switzerland and certain non-European countries (including the US and Canada) can be found online or by contacting us.

USE OF NAVIGATIONAL INFORMATION  
We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Websites and the Subscription Service. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about www.thelordofporn.com.

SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. All Personal Information is protected using appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures.

SOCIAL MEDIA FEATURES  
Our Websites/Apps include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook, Twitter etc. buttons and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our websites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our websites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.

EXTERNAL WEBSITES  
Our Websites provide links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have. Any personal data collected by third party website and/or our affiliate party given by the user shall be the users’ sole responsibility.

PUBLIC FORUMS  
We offer publicly accessible message boards, blogs, and community forums. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through our public message boards, blogs, or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Websites if you so request.

AGE RESTRICTION  
This is an adult review website that expressly and strictly limits its use to adults. This website does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents on this site without exception. If you are under the age of 18 and/or under the age of majority in the jurisdiction you reside and from which you access the website, then your use will be terminated without notice or delay.

COOKIES (OR BROWSER COOKIES).  
A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. The Company uses cookies to enable its servers to recognize your browser and tells the Company how and when you visit the Website and use the Services. For example, the Company uses session ID cookies, which makes it easier for you to navigate the Website. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. The Company also uses persistent cookies, which remain on your hard drive for an extended period. Persistent cookies may be used to store your login information and preferences. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. But if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, the Company’s system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to the Website.

FLASH COOKIES  
Certain features of the Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on the Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, you can access your Flash management tools from Adobe’s website

WEB BEACONS  
Pages of the Website (and the Company’s emails) may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages (or opened an email) and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).  
We do not collect personal information automatically, but it may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

TARGETED ADVERTISING and AD PARTNERS  
Advertising is the predominant way we make money. Advertising revenue allows us to support and improve the Service. We use, and also engage third party ad partners and affiliates who use, [cookie IDs, device IDs (including mobile), hashed email addresses, IP address, ISP and browser information, demographic or interest data, content viewed and actions taken on the Service or Partner Sites, including information about the websites you’ve viewed and advertisements you’ve interacted within in order to provide you with more relevant advertising targeted to your preferences and interests derived from your interaction with the Service, Partner Sites or other third party websites. We may also send you email newsletters and email marketing messages if you have provided us with permission, or consented to receive such emails, as required in the jurisdiction in which you reside.

THIRD-PARTY USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES  
Some content or applications on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.  
We do not control third-party tracking technologies or how third parties’ use them. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

SOCIAL NETWORKS AND THIRD-PARTY PLUGINS  
The Website may include plugins from social networks and other third parties. An example of a plugin is the Facebook© “Like” button. Where legally permitted, these plugins may communicate with and send information to the party that provided the plugin, even if you do not click on the plugin. This information may include your IP address, information about your browser and device, and the address of the webpage you are visiting on the Website. Loading, using, or clicking the plugins may also place, read, and transmit cookies. These cookies may contain a unique identifier the social network or third party assigns you. The loading, functionality, and your use of the plugins are governed by the privacy policy and terms of the party that provided the plugin.

SOCIAL NETWORKS AND THIRD-PARTY SIGNUPS/LOGINS  
The Website allows you to sign up or log in using a social network or other third-party accounts. An example of a third-party signup/login is “Sign Up with Google” / “Login with Google.” Signing up or Logging into the Website with your social network or other third-party account may allow the us to gather information that you give us permission to access from that social network or third party. The signup/login feature may also transfer information to the social network or third party, including your username and password, to authenticate you. The social network or third party may also automatically collect information like your IP address, information about your browser and device, and the address of the webpages you are visiting on the Website. The signup/login feature may also place and read cookies from that third party that may contain a unique identifier the social network or other third party assigns to you. The functionality of and your use of the signup/login is governed by the privacy policy and terms of the party that provided the login functionality.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES  
The Website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other websites. We encourage our customers to be aware when they leave the Website and to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects personally identifiable information.

NO RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES  
This policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Website.

Copyright Infringment  
The Website complies with the Copyright Act. If you reasonably believe that your copyrighted work has been used or posted by a third party without your consent, you may contact us and report it.  
By submitting a copyright infringement notice or other communication (including communications about content stored on or transmitted through the Website), you consent to have these communications forwarded to the person or entity who stored, transmitted, or linked to the content addressed by your communication, to facilitate a prompt resolution

DISCLAIMER  
By the use of the site, the subscriber expressly agrees that the site may use any personal information that has been provided by the user or that has been collected by the site about the user for any purpose, including without limitation, technical, administrative, research and development, customer administration, marketing, trading of personal data, age verification, promotional and advertising use by the websites or third parties authorized to use the information by the Website.  
By the use of the Website, the subscriber expressly agrees that the websites may, in its sole discretion share, disclose, transfer, rent, license or sell any of the personal information about subscribers that it has gathered or collected with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties. All personal information about a subscriber may be collected by a third-party web service provider that has an advertising banner or link on the site.  
The Website is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a subscriber may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the site. The site shall not be responsible for the privacy policy or the content of other such websites. www.thelordofporn.com does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or privacy policies of any of those third-party websites.  
Whenever applicable, each subscriber should seek to read the privacy policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Website.  
All information collected may be shared when necessary to comply with applicable law and /or to cooperate with law enforcement agencies and the courts/tribunals. A user’s IP address may be used to diagnose problems with the server and all other technical issues and to administer the websites.

CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY  
We may change this policy on one or more occasions, and in its sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to this policy. Your continued use of the Website after any change in this policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

CONTACT INFORMATION  
To ask questions or comment about this policy and the Company’s privacy practices, you can contact the Company at info@thelordofporn.com
